so it is week one of the 11-11 challenge
I'm going to try and turn these $1,100
with $11 all the way up to pretty much
Infinity to the highest that I possibly
can and in this challenge I'm going to
be doing it with my whole entire
Community literally there's going to be
endless opportunity to learn from it and
scale from it and there's going to be no
conditions there's no going to be no
hard limit in time and no hard take
profit so I can take my time to achieve
this challenge to the highest coin that
I possibly can but I want to be doing
something a lot more powerful in this
challenge literally every single trade
that I take I'm going to send in my free
telegram so all of you guys make money
alongside with me so join the free
telegram below because every single
trade I take in this challenge you guys
will be able to copy it learn from it
and then scare your account as well and
I'm going to be sharing every single one
of my trades on my Instagram live so you
guys can see the journey happen every
single day so with that being said let's
let this challenge begin so today's the
most important day out of the whole
entire week which is actually Sunday you
guys can see it it's currently Sunday at
midnight because because this is where I
set up the pairs that I'm going to be
trading for the week ahead and it's a
lot easier to follow during the week so
let's get started so the first pair that
we have right now is USD CHF you guys
can tell USD CHF what I'm going to be
looking for is for Longs currently we
have a left head right shoulder at this
area of Interest basically what I'm
waiting for is for literally price to
just dip into this area hit my alarm at
9134 and giveing my entry signal so I
take the trade the second trade is going
to be
audusd which all time time frames are
currently now looking bullish we only
have the 4H hour that is bearish but we
have to wait for that time frame to
shift that's why I have here that I'm
waiting for we have two time frames in
syn for it to shift so what I'm waiting
for right now is for literally price to
basically do something like this once
price has a rejection from here I need a
retest for then it to head to the upside
this will probably take a day or two and
then last but not least is going to be
audcad so AUD CAD what I'm waiting for
is for price to make it to this area of
Interest it hit my daily EMA may it hit
round psychological level
87500 so I can take this trade so I need
for price to be able to actually dip
down a little bit lower into this area
so I have my entry to then take this
trade to the upside so those are my top
three pairs for this week and let's
actually wait for that stuff to happen
so we can enter the trade and scale this
account currently right now which on
Sunday we are still at 1111 on the
balance and like always let's make sure
everything is legit so let me show you
guys that my Facebook account right here
you guys can see that we have the
starting balance of $1,100 and11 this
updated 23 minutes ago and obviously
there is no data because we haven't
taken the account yet so let's let this
challenge begin market update on the
1111 challenge it is currently 9:40 in
the morning and last night's trade was
missed you guys can see how it pulled
back to
90134 exactly how I anticipated last
night so haven't taken this trade yet
and then AUD USD which is the second
pair on the watch watch this I'm going
to simply be waiting for a quick little
break and retest as of right now no
trades so it's currently 1:23 in the
morning so we had the little pullback on
USD CHF as we anticipated back to retest
the EMA so I'm looking to enter the
trade literally in the next 30 minutes
right before London session going to be
looking for any clean rejection
candlesticks from right now the 1 hour
EMA so I can take the trade long this is
our 1 hour EMA that blue line that is
right there I'm going to be waiting for
anything so we can enter the trade so
and head to the upside and then next we
have
audusd which we are just waiting for
price to go above this area come back
and then retest it and then head to the
upside or at this area I'm just going to
be waiting for some rejection
candlesticks to then head to the upside
so as of right now still looking very
very good Monday night all right guys so
we actually caught a trade on the 11-11
challenge we could have not asked for a
more perfect entry and it's exactly what
I explained to you guys last night at
1:23 in the morning I actually woke up
early today and I C the trade was into a
little bit of drw down and then it ended
up moving very fast so let me show you
guys so this is currently how we're
looking on the 11-11 challenge we are up
$1,700 so the trade that I explained at
this area of Interest was happening
perfectly we had price that went up we
had price that came down gave me the
rejection and then we entered the trade
you guys can see right here this is my
rejection this is also known as a
inverted head and shoulders so this is
the left head and the right shoulder
which is when the market changes
Direction and then we have the news that
pushed it up perfectly and extremely
fast so I'm going to be looking to maybe
hold for a little bit longer and if not
I'm going to close I'm going to see if
price has a pull back into here to then
retest it and head to the upside so stay
tuned so it is currently 11:00 in the
afternoon now so the account is pretty
much up double or a little bit over
double and we have continued to head to
the upside so we haven't had the
retracement that I've been expecting but
it's just continued to head up so it's
gone over well my take profit and what I
expect expected to get in this trade so
now we're reaching this very strong
level of resistance which price if Taps
it under we can reject it so that's why
I'm going to be getting out pretty much
in the next 15 to 20 minutes of this
trade so going to be closing out very
very soon these current profits right
now it's currently right now 10:00
getting on the plane going to
Brazil trade
update trade update right now currently
we closed the trade out right now this
is how the TR trade would have played
out on
audusd would have literally flown to a
take profit so pretty much done for the
week it took one trade we flipped the
account
to
3,400 so we're done for the week all
right so right now trade update no
service but who cares we made 80k
yesterday so we don't have to trade
fire
Brazil that's
[Music]
[Applause]
it all right so trade up day it is
currently Thursday
1:42 p.m. so Miami time I think we are
12:00 or 11:00 and we're still here in
Brazil the Rio you guys are probably
wondering what happened yesterday and
Steve invited me out to Brazil bro
Steve's crazy like yo we're going to go
to the favellas and we're going to go
give out some cash and I'm like bro
under one circumstance and that's if
this trade hits takeprofit which it did
so we pulled up so trade update like I
told you guys on Tuesday or Monday I'm
like you know what done for the week we
don't need to trade the account anymore
anymore the account is currently at
about 3,000 something
3,461 so we no longer have to trade the
account or personally I'm good with
these profits for the week so let me
show you guys the trade basically what I
explained we came up hit the takeprofit
and now we're going to have the
retracement I've been waiting for price
to retest this level here so I can take
the trade up but if not I would then
just be waiting for price to break and
then retest ahead to the upside so
pretty simple week and uh we're going to
go back to the fetas now to meet the
boss boss that actually might come out
in the other channel that we got so stay
[Music]
tuned all right so we just landed right
now from Brazil really long trip crazy
the faas is something that not only did
I ever think I was ever going to go but
be able to actually like connect and go
all the way to the top like that so this
trading week was pretty boring I told
you guys we caught one trade at the
beginning of the week and that's it and
it actually paid out pretty good because
it ended up you know happening very fast
the news ended up getting our trade to a
takeprofit and we flipped the account so
the account is exactly in the same exact
spot which is
3,4
and $61 so we are exactly the same as we
started the week and right now it is
currently Friday well 1 p.m. right now
so you guys can see Friday 1 p.m. so we
just got word right now that we have to
go to Vegas for F1 we're going to go
with Steve Neil maybe the full s guys
and I honestly hate Vegas every single
time I go it's uh not the best time but
we got to go for F1 I didn't make to the
F1 in Miami I was traveling so now let's
go to Vegas for the F1 so let's see how
we trade in Vegas let's go all right so
we're here in Vegas let's do a quick
recap the car has just pulled up so you
guys already know this is the 11-11
challenge which I have no goal in terms
of Target a where I want to flip this
account of where you know how long it's
going to take me my goal is to just help
you guys you guys see all the trades I
take you guys copy them learn from them
that's why every single trade that I
take I'm sending it in the free telegram
that's why you guys could also see that
I only took one trade this week because
the goal is to just scale the account
over time the goal is not to flip it
super fast from one day to another so
that's why this week we actually made
$2,350 in one trade like you know what
that's it I literally flipped the
account to more than what I even had in
mind cuz I didn't really have a take
profit I just wanted to win the first
trade so we got a little bit more
cushion in the car our car is here which
I'm freezing by the way is going um so
we ended up risking I think it was about
like 40% of the so we ended up risking
about like two three $400 of the actual
account and then we ended up making
$2,350 on that account which led us to
have a total of
$3,460 in that account which we just
didn't trade for the rest of the week so
now we're going to go to the hit the gym
with Steve and uh probably stay here
another week in Vegas who knows but
that's the power of said and forget the
power of the 11-11 and working with a
purpose because you guys can see you
guys just saw Steve Steve just turned
10K into half a million dollars live in
a kick stream because he was doing it
for a purpose his purpose was to pay
back Dana White's debt cuz Dana White
had a half a million dollar debt and he
paid it back and I saw everything there
live so when you guys decide to start
your own challenge you guys start to do
whatever you want do it with a purpose
so the goal of this challenge is for me
to just help you guys and show you guys
every single trade that I take is legit
and you guys can learn from it and scale
your account with it so let's go ahead
and check so that's all for this week if
you want to know more about about the
setup forget strategy and how I get the
results like these or these click the
link in the description below I have a
video that explains to you exactly what
the setup forget strategy consists of
how hundreds of my students are making
,000 to $1,500 a week as a beginner set
forget Trader literally if you don't
know anything about trading within the
first 3 months using the set foret
strategy you can make anywhere from
$1,000 to $11,500 a week so click the
link in the description below so you
guys know exactly what the center for
actually means and how you can be part
of the community so I'll see you guys
next week on the 1111 t